[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first name of Mr Burton, who played Geordi La Forge in Star Trek: The Next Generation?", "correct_answer": "LeVar", "incorrect_answers": ["Labatt", "Limahl", "Lamar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Keyboards are used for the input of text and characters.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hummingbirds are the only birds on the planet to have this amazing ability.", "correct_answer": "They can fly backwards.", "incorrect_answers": ["They can stay without water for as many as 30 days.", "All of these", "They can carry food that is 3 times heavier than their own weight."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Midnight Run, how much money does Jonathan Mardukas embezzle from Las Vegas gangster Jimmy Serrano?", "correct_answer": "15 million", "incorrect_answers": ["50 million", "1 million", "23 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the beginning of the film The Pursuit of Happyness, what does Chris do for a living?", "correct_answer": "He sells bone density scanners.", "incorrect_answers": ["He repairs medical equipment.", "He sells Metalife door to door.", "He sells CAT scan machines."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kevin Spacey plays the elusive kingpin Keyser S\u00f6ze in this cult classic movie.", "correct_answer": "The Usual Suspects", "incorrect_answers": ["Mafia Wars", "Lions Den", "Blood and Guts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what European city is the popular bronze statue Capitoline Wolf located?", "correct_answer": "Rome", "incorrect_answers": ["Madrid", "Paris", "London"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did  engineer James Wright  invent in 1943?", "correct_answer": "Silly Putty", "incorrect_answers": ["The oral polio vaccine", "The first chemical to repel sharks", "Acetate cartoon cells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "German-born princess, Sophie Augusta Fredericka of Anhalt-Zerbst, reigned as Empress of what country, from June 28, 1762 until her death?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "England", "Austria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Born in Vladivostok, Russia in 1920, this Academy Award-winning actor is best know for playing King Mongkut of Siam 4,626 times onstage. He also reprised the role in the film version of the musical.", "correct_answer": "Yul Brenner", "incorrect_answers": ["Telly Savalas", "Lee J. Cobb", "Peter Sellers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "May 13th is the National Fibromyalgia Associations Fibromyalgia Awareness Day.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the motel where Tina Turner stayed after she left Ike Turner in the hotel room?", "correct_answer": "The Ramada Inn", "incorrect_answers": ["Super 8", "Days Inn", "Motel 6"]}]